{
    "subject": "resource/Murder_of_Elisa_Izquierdo",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/New_York",
    "human_readable": "The murder of Elisa Izquierdo occurred in New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8233479261398315,
            "question": "What year did the murder of Elisa Izquierdo occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.814517080783844,
            "question": "Are there any known details about the perpetrator of Elisa Izquierdo's murder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7998348474502563,
            "question": "Where did the murder of Elisa Izquierdo take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.759064257144928,
            "question": "What happened to Elisa Izquierdo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6338767409324646,
            "question": "Has there been any legal action taken regarding the murder of Elisa Izquierdo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.62861168384552,
            "question": "Was the murder of Elisa Izquierdo a high-profile case?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5894461274147034,
            "question": "What impact did the murder of Elisa Izquierdo have on the community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4836934208869934,
            "question": "Is there a memorial or tribute dedicated to Elisa Izquierdo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44051873683929443,
            "question": "What can be learned from the case of Elisa Izquierdo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.011961448937654495,
            "question": "Are there any organizations working to prevent similar tragedies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The murder of Elisa Izquierdo occurred in New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3745_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can be learned from the case of Elisa Izquierdo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3745_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a memorial or tribute dedicated to Elisa Izquierdo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3745_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did the murder of Elisa Izquierdo have on the community?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3745_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3745_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer to your query:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents support that the murder of Elisa Izquierdo occurred in New York, as it is stated multiple times throughout the text that she was a six-year-old girl from New York City who died due to child abuse by her mother."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the case of Elisa Izquierdo, including that she was a six-year-old girl from New York City who died from severe abuse by her mother. While specific details such as the exact location or date are not provided in the given context, it is clear that the documents discuss events related to Elisa Izquierdo's tragic death in New York, which supports the statement that her murder occurred in New York."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}